// File: src/data/questions.js
const questions = {
  security: [
    { question: "What is your primary method for securing your device?", answer: "Use strong passwords and enable two-factor authentication." },
    { question: "How do you handle suspicious emails or messages?", answer: "Avoid clicking on links and report the email to your IT department." },
    { question: "What steps do you take to protect your passwords?", answer: "Store passwords in a secure password manager and never share them." }
  ],
  safety: [
    { question: "What safety equipment do you use in your workplace?", answer: "Use helmets, gloves, and safety goggles as required." },
    { question: "How do you ensure personal safety while working alone?", answer: "Inform someone of your location and check in periodically." },
    { question: "What is your protocol for reporting hazards?", answer: "Report hazards to your supervisor immediately and document them." }
  ],
  firstAid: [
    { question: "How do we treat someone who feels fainting", answer: "Elevate the legs" },
    { question: "How do you treat a burn injury?", answer: "Cool the burn under running water and cover it with a clean cloth." },
    { question: "What should you do if someone is choking?", answer: "Perform the Heimlich maneuver or encourage them to cough." },
    {question:"What are the PDI's of water glycol?", answer: "1. Stowage, 2. Quandity, 3. Wire seal on handle is intact, 4. Cartige is visible in handle"},
    {question:"What are the PDI's of halon?", answer: "1. Stowage, 2. Quandity, 3. Preassure gauge must be in the serviceable band, 4. Pin is secure in the handle"},
    {question:"What are the PDI's of fire gloves?", answer: "1. Stowage, 2. Quandity, 3. No scroch marks, 4. One left ine right"},
    {question:"What are the PDI's of torch?", answer: "1. Stowage, 2. Quandity, 3. No scroch marks, 4. Red light flashes at not more than 10 seconds"},
    {question:"What are the PDI's of portsble oxygen mask?", answer: "1. Stowage, 2. Quandity, 3. Strap is present, 4. Gauge reads 3/4 to full, 5. Mask attached to Hi flow for emergency use bottles, 6. Mask attached to low flow for therapeutic use bottles, 7. Spare mask is present"},
  ]
};

export default questions;
